# **Serhiy Shainyuk**

### **Front-End Developer**

- sj.shaynyuk@gmail.com
- Sh.Sergiy
- +3 8(063) 443-83-18
- SergiGan/HubFrEnd
- Viv, Ukraine



First of all, experience is, a collection of everything that happens to a person in her life and that she is conscious; people can have experience about themselves, their abilities, their virtues and vices, and people can also have experience and ideas, ideas and knowledge. So I'm open to people if they are ready for it, to knowledge, experience and everything new that makes the world a better one. I strive for excellence, critical thinking, versatility in their interests. I am interested in the latest technologies, in particular in the field of information technology, as well as software optimization and participation in its development. Motivation by the challengei and non-standard tasks. Why in IT, is because modern life can not be imagined without the latest technology and self-improvement.

#### **SKILLs**

#### Software

HTML/CSS

mastered by 85%

Bootstrap

mastered by 70%

**JavaScript** 

mastered by 55%

**JQuery** 

50%

Angular 7\*)

<u>ng/exam</u>

Fortran

70%

Sublime Text

mastered by 85%

Quoda

I use 65%

Koala

٥.

DreamViewer

got skills 80%

Photoshop

AutoCad

6:

3DPipe

90%

PC Stadyo

90%

ANSYS/Mechanical/Structural

35%

### Education

SkillUp IT Specialist Training Center

**Angular 7** 

\*2019

SkillUp IT Specialist Training Center

Front-End

2019

"Prometheus"

This is a Ukrainian public project for mass open online

courses

The course of "Fundamentals of Information Security"

2015

Ivan Franko Lviv National University Faculty of Physics and Electronics, physics specialist

2001-2006

. . .

# Experience

PrAT "TehEnergo" Leading Engineer in the diagnostics department of the equipment

2016present

PrAT "LvivOrgres"

**Engineer for Safe Maintenance of Power Equipment** 

2008-2016

Publishing House "World of Physics"

Text layout and editing

2006-2008